[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Choose mandatory components to build a PC. (MULTIPLE ANSWERS)",
        "options": [
            "CPU FAN",
            "NIC CARD",
            "HARD DISK",
            "THERMAL PASTE"
        ],
        "correct": "CPU FAN, HARD DISK"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Anti-Static Mat will help prevent?",
        "options": [
            "ESD Damage",
            "Direct Fault",
            "Shock",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": "ESD Damage"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Does RAM work on ZIF mechanism?",
        "options": [
            "YES",
            "NO"
        ],
        "correct": "NO"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What can you use to clean a CPU?",
        "options": [
            "Water",
            "Distilled Water",
            "Isopropyl Alcohol",
            "All of the Above"
        ],
        "correct": "Isopropyl Alcohol"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What are two cables required while installing a SATA HARD DISK?",
        "options": [
            "SATA Data Cable",
            "Sata Ethernet Cable",
            "Sata Power Cable",
            "Molex Cable"
        ],
        "correct": "SATA Data Cable, Sata Power Cable"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Where do you connect power LED and reset lights?",
        "options": [
            "USB PINS",
            "COMMS PINS",
            "PANAL PINS",
            "SATA"
        ],
        "correct": "PANAL PINS"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What is used to clean the heat sink of a computer?",
        "options": [
            "Compressed Air",
            "Isopropyl Alcohol",
            "Water",
            "Lint Free Cloth"
        ],
        "correct": "Compressed Air"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "What class of fire extinguisher is used to extinguish electrical equipment fires?",
        "options": [
            "Class A",
            "Water Based Fire Extinguisher",
            "Non-Water Based Fire Extinguisher",
            "Class D"
        ],
        "correct": "Non-Water Based Fire Extinguisher"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Which of the following actions should you not perform if you want to prevent your computer from any type of ESD while servicing the computer? (CHOOSE TWO)",
        "options": [
            "Wear an antistatic wrist band",
            "Keep one hand in contact with the bare metal frame of the computer at all times.",
            "Make sure that the room in which the computer is serviced is carpeted.",
            "Use metal objects on the motherboard."
        ],
        "correct": "Make sure that the room in which the computer is serviced is carpeted, Use metal objects on the motherboard."
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which of the following is high-voltage equipment? (Select all that apply)",
        "options": [
            "Printers",
            "CRTs",
            "PSUs",
            "Hard Drive"
        ],
        "correct": "Printers, PSUs"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "The risk of electrostatic discharge is the greatest at?",
        "options": [
            "Daytime",
            "Night Time",
            "High Humidity",
            "Low Humidity"
        ],
        "correct": "Low Humidity"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Which condition refers to a sudden and dramatic increase in voltage for a long period of time?",
        "options": [
            "Sag",
            "Surge",
            "Blackout",
            "Spike"
        ],
        "correct": "Surge"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Which is the first step of troubleshooting?",
        "options": [
            "Find Cause",
            "Data backup",
            "List Causes",
            "Eliminate Cause"
        ],
        "correct": "Data backup"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Device Manager contains?",
        "options": [
            "Device and device driver information",
            "Disk Tools",
            "Error check",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": "Device and device driver information"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "How to identify a problem if the power-on self-test fails?",
        "options": [
            "Check BIOS",
            "Error Message",
            "Beep Code",
            "Event Log"
        ],
        "correct": "Beep Code"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "A hierarchical database that stores low-level settings for the Microsoft Windows operating system.",
        "options": [
            "Windows Resistry",
            "Windows Registry",
            "Device Manager",
            "MBR Boot Loader"
        ],
        "correct": "Windows Registry"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "Which of the following is the true layer of Software architecture in terms of OS?",
        "options": [
            "1. Application Software, 2. Operating system, 3. Hardware",
            "1. Hardware, 2. Operating system, 3. Application Software",
            "1. Operating system, 2. Kernel, 3. Application Software",
            "1. Application Software, 2. Hardware, 3. Operating System"
        ],
        "correct": "1. Hardware, 2. Operating system, 3. Application Software"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "Which of the following is not an operating system?",
        "options": [
            "Linux",
            "DOS",
            "Microsoft LT",
            "Windows NT"
        ],
        "correct": "Microsoft LT"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "What is the Full Form of FAT?",
        "options": [
            "File Attribute Table",
            "Font Attribute Table",
            "File Action Table",
            "File Allocation Table"
        ],
        "correct": "File Allocation Table"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "The maximum file size of FAT32 is?",
        "options": [
            "4 MB",
            "4 GHz",
            "4 GB",
            "4 TB"
        ],
        "correct": "4 GB"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "Which of the following is not a term used in OS?",
        "options": [
            "Multi-RAID",
            "Multi-Tasking",
            "Multi-Processing",
            "Multi-Threading"
        ],
        "correct": "Multi-RAID"
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "Which of the following is not an architecture of CPU?",
        "options": [
            "x64",
            "x86",
            "arm64",
            "amd57"
        ],
        "correct": "amd57"
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "Registers can be used in CPU to?",
        "options": [
            "store CPU instruction",
            "store user data",
            "store virtual page",
            "none of the above"
        ],
        "correct": "store CPU instruction"
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "Minimum required RAM for Windows 10 64-bit is?",
        "options": [
            "1GB",
            "3GB",
            "2GB",
            "512MB"
        ],
        "correct": "2GB"
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "What do you mean by partition in drive?",
        "options": [
            "Logical Fragmentation of drive",
            "Fragmented drive",
            "Logical division of drive",
            "I don't know"
        ],
        "correct": "Logical division of drive"
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "Which registry file contains information about the hardware and software in the computer system?",
        "options": [
            "HKEY_CLASSES_ROOT",
            "HKEY_CURRENT_USER",
            "HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE",
            "HKEY_USERS"
        ],
        "correct": "HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE"
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "Check the True statements.",
        "options": [
            "There can be multiple HOST OS",
            "There can be multiple GUEST OS",
            "There can only be one GUEST OS",
            "There can be only one HOST OS"
        ],
        "correct": "There can be multiple GUEST OS"
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "Which of the following is a network OS?",
        "options": [
            "Windows 7",
            "Windows 10",
            "Windows Server",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "correct": "Windows Server"
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "Virtual Memory is?",
        "options": [
            "Logical RAM",
            "Virtual Box RAM",
            "Fragmented RAM",
            "Contiguous RAM"
        ],
        "correct": "Logical RAM"
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "Which of the following is not a Windows default tool?",
        "options": [
            "Event Viewer",
            "Performance Monitor",
            "Cache Cleaner",
            "Disk Cleanup"
        ],
        "correct": "Cache Cleaner"
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "Which partition can hold an operating system?",
        "options": [
            "Extended partition",
            "Unallocated partition",
            "Primary partition",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": "Primary partition"
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": ".ISO is the extension for what kind of file?",
        "options": [
            "Word file",
            "Disk image file",
            "Portable document file",
            "Virtual box setup file"
        ],
        "correct": "Disk image file"
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "Drive Label A and B is reserved for?",
        "options": [
            "SSD",
            "Floppy Drive",
            "CD Drive",
            "DVD Drive"
        ],
        "correct": "Floppy Drive"
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "A hard disk is divided into tracks which are further subdivided into?",
        "options": [
            "Clusters",
            "Sectors",
            "Vectors",
            "Heads"
        ],
        "correct": "Sectors"
    }
    
    
]